Guide to the Washington Square Park (New York, N.Y.) and Washington Square Area Image Collection, 1850-1990 NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001
New York University Archives
- Series IV: Washington Square Campus Buildings
  - Coles Sports Center
    - Coles Sports Center, Closure Due to City Repair of Broadway Water Main, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6415; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 4x7 inches (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 77)
    - Coles Sports Center, Prescription Exercise Facility, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6417; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 4x7 inches (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 78)
    - Coles Sports Center, BPA Casebook, Female Student Weightlifiting with Spotter, 1985; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6419; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 79)
    - Coles Sports Center, BPA Viewbook Three Students at Signup Desk, 1986-1987; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6421; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 80)
    - Coles Sports Center, Sehnap Bulletin, Students Swimming in Lanes, 1986-1987; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6423; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 81)
      New York University |x Buildings.; New York University. School of Education, Health, Nursing, and Arts Profession.; New York University. Washington Square Campus.
    - Coles Sports Center, Basketball Courts Looking South, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6425; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 82)
    - Coles Sports Center, Weight Room, Female Student Using Upper Body Exercise Equipment Closeup, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6427; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches; Giese, Al (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 83)
    - Coles Sports Center, Summer Bulletin, Three Students on Squash Court, 1986; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6429; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 84)
    - Coles Sports Center, Summer Bulletin, Male Student in Wheelchair Riding Up Handicap Ramp, 1986; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6431; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 85)
    - Coles Sports Center, Female Students Playing Basketball, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6433; Black and White Print, (Photoraph), 8x10 inches (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 86)
    - Coles Sports Center, Man Posing with Basketballs on Basketball Court, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6435; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 87)
    - Coles Sports Center, Student Jumping and Throwing Basketball at Hoop, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6437; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 88)
    - Coles Sports Center, Joint School Project Students Using Coles, Two Students Playing Basketball, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6439; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 89)
    - Coles Sports Center, Male Students Playing Basketball, Aerial Shot, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6441; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 90)
    - Coles Sports Center, NYU Basketball Game Versus Queens College, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6443; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 91)
    - Coles Sports Center, Rhythmic Gymnastics Performance, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6444; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 92)
    - Coles Sports Center, Students in Zeta Psi Fraternity, circa 1980; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6447; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 11x14 inches (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 93)
    - Coles Sports Center, Two Female Students Smiling, circa 1980; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6449 (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 94)
    - Coles Sports Center, Basketball Court with Students, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6450 (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 95)
  - Deutsches Haus
    - Deutsches Haus Goethe Institute at NYU, Interior Staircase, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6452; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - Deutsches Haus Goethe Institute at NYU, Sitting Room, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6454; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - Deutsches Haus Goethe Institute at NYU, Auditorium with Piano, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6456; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 3)
    - Deutsches Haus, Front Door and Building Facade, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6458; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 4)
    - Deutsches Haus, Front Door Close-up, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6460; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 5)
    - Deutsches Haus Goethe Institute at NYU, View of Courtyard Through Doorway, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6462; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 6)
    - Deutsches Haus, People Standing in Front of the Building, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6464; Black and White print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 7)
    - Deutsches Haus, Facade, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6467; Black and White print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 8)
    - Deutsches Haus, Seen Through Arch, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6469; Black and White print (Photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 8)
    - Deutsches Haus, Overhead View with Students, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6471; Color Print (photograph), 4 x 6 inches (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 9)
      New York University |x Buildings.; New York University |x Students.; New York University. Washington Square Campus.
    - Deutsches Haus, At Night, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6373; Black and White print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 10)
    - Deutsches Haus, Sign Over Door, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6475; Black and White print, (Photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 11)
    - Deutsches Haus, Proposed Site, June 4, 1969; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6478; Black and White print (Photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 12)
  - East Building
    - East Building, Entrance, 1965; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6481; Black and White print (Photograph), 3.5 x 4.25 inches (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - East Building, Washington Place and Greene Street, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6484; Sepia Print (Photograph), 4.5 x 6.5 inches (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - East Building and Book Center, c. 1930s; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6486; Black and White print (photograph), 8 x10 inches (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 3)
    - East Building, Corner of Washington and Greene St, 1927; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6488; Sepia print (photograph), 4.75 x 6.75 (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 4)
    - Student Health Center: Health Services Reception Area, 1969; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6500; Black and White Print (photograph), 6.25 x 9 inches (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 5)
      Medical care.; New York University. Washington Square Campus.; Student activities.
    - East Building: Intramural Floor, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6502; Black and White Print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 6)
      New York University |x Athletics.; New York University |x Buildings.; New York University. Washington Square Campus.
    - East Building, Entrance, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6504 (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 7)
  - Education, School of (Box 5, Folder 3, Item 1)
    - School of Education Building, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6510; Color Print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 5, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - One Fifth Avenue - Exteriors
    - One Fifth Ave., Exterior with Police Baricades, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6512; Black and White Print (photograph), 3.5 x 5.5 inches (Box 5, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - One Fifth Avenue, Exterior with Police Barricade, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6514; Black and White Print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 5, Folder 4, Item 2)
    - One Fifth Ave., Building Exterior, Seen Above Street Level, 1965; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6516; Black and White Print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 5, Folder 4, Item 3)
    - One Fifth Ave., Exterior, East Side of Fifth Ave. Looking North from Washington Square North, 1948; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6519; Black and White print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 5, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - One Fifth Ave., East Side of Fifth Ave., Looking South Toward Washington Sq. Park From West Eighth St., 1948; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6521; Black and White Print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 5, Folder 4, Item 5)
    - One Fifth Ave., Looking Southeast From w. 8th St., 1948; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6523; Black and White Print (Photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 5, Folder 4, Item 6)
    - One Fifth Avenue Hotel, East Side of Fifth Avenue, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6525; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 5, Folder 4, Item 7)
    - One Fifth Ave., Exterior, Looking North at Empire State Building, May 10, 1963; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6527; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches; Simmons, William R. (Box 5, Folder 4, Item 8)
    - One Fifth Ave., Building Facade, Looking East, May 5, 1966; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6529; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 14 x 11 inches (Box 5, Folder 4, Item 9)
    - One Fifth Ave., Exterior, Bike Lanes, October 1980; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6531; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches; Chin, Danny (Box 5, Folder 4, Item 10)
    - One Fifth. Ave., Block University Place, Looking Northeast from Beneach Arch at Washington Square North, circa 1948; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6533; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches
  - Two Fifth Avenue
    - Two Fifth Ave., Chancellor Chase's Residence until January 1940, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6536; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 5, Folder 5, Item 1)
    - Two Fifth Ave., Dr. Chase's Residence until January 1940, Courtyard with Fountain, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6538; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 5, Folder 5, Item 2)
    - Two Fifth Ave., South Side of West 8th Street looking West from Fifth Avenue, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6540; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 5, Folder 5, Item 3)
    - Two Fifth Ave., Chancellor Chase's Residence Until January 1940, Courtyard in the Snow, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6542; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 5, Folder 5, Item 4)
    - Two Fifth Ave., Dr. Chase's Residence up to January 1940, View of Backyard, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6544; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 5, Folder 5, Item 5)
    - Block Fifth Avenue, West Side of Fifth Ave. Looking North From Washington Square North, 1947; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6546; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 5, Folder 5, Item 6)
  - Fifth Ave. #24
    - Fifth Ave. # 24, Entrance Doorway, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6549; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 5, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - Courant Institute
    - Courant Building, Looking Northwest, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6522; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 1)
    - Warren Weaver Hall Under Construction, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6554; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 2)
    - Courant, Gould Plaza, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6556; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 3)
    - Courant, Looking Northwest, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6558; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 4)
    - Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, Building Sign, November 1972; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6560; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 5)
    - Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, Aerial, Looking East, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6562 (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 6)
    - Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, Looking Southeast, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6568; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 7)
    - Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, Looking Southwest, 1973; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6570; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 8)
  - D'Agostino Hall Artist's Rendering/Plans
    - Filomen D'Agostino Hall, Artist's Rendering, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6564; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches; Pagnano, Patrick D. (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 1)
    - Filomen D'Agostino Hall, Artist's Rendering Closeup, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6566; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches; Pagnano, Patrick D. (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 2)